adotas.com 2006-10-04

# Adotas » Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

**How do I subscribe to your newsletter?**  
Just type your name, email and company name in the text boxes on the left near the top of the site, and click subscribe.

**Why do you need my email address?**  
So we know where to send the newsletter.  
**  
Why do you need my name and company name?**  
To see which companies have people subscribing to our newsletter.

**Do you share or sell my personal information with anyone else?**  
We don’t sell your personal information or share it with any third parties. We do send advertisements from third party companies in our newsletter, but this comes from us.

**What do you consider personal information?**  
Any piece of information that can be used to uniquely identify you, such as your name or email address.

**How can I unsubscribe from your email newsletter?**  
There’s an unsubscribe link at the bottom of every issue. Just click that link and follow the instructions on the next page.

**What else do you keep track of?**  
We use cookies to anonymously track traffic through our site. Your web browser also provides information such as your IP address, browser version and language. All of this is anonymous.

**Do your advertisers track me?**  
We’re an ad-supported business. Our advertising provider may also use cookies to track consumer information and provide ads that you might find useful.  
**  
What is a cookie?**  
It’s a small text file placed on your computer by a web page. It helps us track consumer information and can’t be read by any other web page.

**Can cookies hurt my computer?**  
Cookies can neither harm your computer, nor deliver viruses. Can I delete a cookie? Certainly. It depends on what internet browser you’re using, but they’re usually found in the same place as your temporary internet files. You can also set your browser’s security preferences to automatically reject cookies.
